top of page

Privacy Policy
==============

ITExpress may share the following categories of Personal Information with Third Party Service Providers for a business purpose: identifiers, including name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, internet protocol address, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers.

​

ITExpress respects the privacy of our clients in our mobile applications, our website [https://uni-accounting.com](https://uni-accounting.com/) and our Business Software. Based on Article 13 of the Swiss Federal Constitution and the data protection provisions of the federal government (Data Protection Act, DSG), everyone has the right to the protection of their privacy and protection against misuse of their personal data. We adhere to these regulations.

In close cooperation with our hosting providers, we strive to protect the databases as well as possible against unauthorized access, loss, misuse or falsification.

We also invest in initiatives such as the Coalition for Better Ads, the Google News Initiative, and ads.txt in order to support a healthy, sustainable ads ecosystem.

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We will alert you about any changes by updating the 'Last updated' date of this Privacy Policy.

Financial data (Mobile apps and Business Software):

When you enter data, such as accounts, payments and transfers, into the app yourself, the data is stored in a protected local database on your mobile device or on your computer (for our Business Software). The data is not transmitted to us or passed on to third parties. To delete the financial data in the local database, uninstall the mobile app. For the Business Software, the local database and backups can be deleted.

Some of our mobile apps have the possibility to access personal photos, and use calendars to set dates in the app.

Last updated: 12/18/2021

​

ITExpress Ltd.

Calvin 8

CH-2540 Grenchen

​

​​

​​

© Copyright 2024 ITExpress Ltd.

bottom of page
